http://www.milestonesinrecovery.com/privacy-statement/

Privacy Statement - South Florida Eating Disorder Treatment Center
EventsMeet Our StaffOur FacilitiesArticlesEating Disorder TreatmentContactPrivacy Statement
Call (800) 347-2364 PRIVACY STATEMENTYour privacy is important to Milestones in Recovery. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that Milestones collects, and the ways in which Milestones uses that personal information.Personal information collectionMilestones may collect and use the following kinds of personal information: information about your use of this website or information that you provide for the purpose of registering and using the website  information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services (including downloading books, information requests; and any other information that you send to Milestones in RecoveryUsing personal informationMilestones in Recovery may use your personal information to:administer this website;personalize the website for you;enable your access to and use of the website services; publish information about you on the website; send to you products that you purchase or request; send you marketing communications.Where Milestones in Recovery discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, Milestones in Recovery may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.Securing your dataMilestones will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.Milestones will store all the personal information you provide on secure servers.Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be protected by encryption technology.Cross-border data transfersInformation that Milestones collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which Milestones or its web contractors operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world.You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.Updating this statementMilestones in Recovery may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.Other websitesThis website contains links to other websites.Milestones in Recovery is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.Contact Milestones in RecoveryIf you have any questions about this privacy policy or Milestones in Recovery’s treatment of your personal information, please write:by email to mlerner@milestonesprogram.org; or by post to 2525 Embassy Drive, Suite 10, Cooper City, FL 33026.This document was created using a Contractology template available at http://www.freenetlaw.com.Free eBook “A Guide To Eating Disorder Recovery”
I am Interested In*Food Addiction TreatmentBulimia TreatmentAnorexia TreatmentBED Treatment Latest News Mental Health Professionals Can Become a Certified Food Addiction Counselor at INFACT Big Book Alumni Meeting – Wed. Oct. 7, 2020 Milestones Now Accepts Tricare Milestones’ Telehealth Option Now Available for Alumni Start Your Journey to Recovery! Call (800) 347-2364
© Copyright 2020 Milestones in Recovery. | All Rights Reserved. Privacy Statement
Developed by WordPress ExpertNews16Sep 20Mental Health Professionals Can Become a Certified Food Addiction Counselor at INFACT Why INFACT? INFACT training allows you to learn from nine of the world's leading Food Addiction experts. “No other Food... Read More 1 2 3 … 10 Next »
